businessinsider.sg 2019-12-24

# Personal Data Protection Statement - Singapore Press Holdings

Singapore Press Holdings Ltd and its related corporations (“SPH”) aim to comply with the requirements of the [Personal Data Protection Act 2012](https://sso.agc.gov.sg/Act/PDPA2012) (“PDPA”) and respect your choices in respect of your personal data.

The main purposes for which your personal data is collected, used or disclosed by SPH and its service providers in Singapore include providing you with our products and services, managing your subscriptions, renewals and your account, processing payments, addressing questions and feedback, improving our products and services, as well as where permitted under law, sending you marketing and promotional offers on products and services, and personalized content and advertising based on your preferences or demographics. 

In addition, if you have registered your telephone number with the national Do Not Call (DNC) registry, we will not send you promotional and marketing messages via your telephone number unless you have provided SPH consent to do so. 

SPH has a Data Protection Policy which provides more information about how we collect, use and disclose your personal data. Should you have any feedback or enquiries relating to your personal data or if you wish to stop receiving promotional or marketing messages from SPH, please contact:

The Personal Data Protection Officer at the following addresses:

Name: Mr Colin Low, Chief Data Protection Officer  
Email : [dataprotection@sph.com.sg](mailto:dataprotection@sph.com.sg)  
Postal Address: [1000 Toa Payoh North](https://www.google.com/maps/place/1000+Toa+Payoh+N,+Singapore+Press+Holdings,+Singapore+318994/@1.3430597,103.8464293,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x31da176b08f0b50d:0x6fc45c2cc2e21b27!8m2!3d1.3430597!4d103.848618), News Centre, Singapore 318994  
Telephone Number : 63198555

For more information about PDPA generally, please visit the Personal Data Protection Commission’s website at [http://www.pdpc.gov.sg](http://www.pdpc.gov.sg/)

**If you are an European Union Data Subject, you may wish to review thePrivacy Policy Statement  that addresses how we manage personal data in accordance with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).**

(Last updated 15 October 2018)
